export const chapter = "Chapter - 9: Features of Artificial Intelligence";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What distinguishes smart gadgets from other household machines?",
          optionA: "Price",
          optionB: "Features",
          optionC: "Size",
          correctAnswer: "Features",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of voice assistance technology?",
          optionA: "Microwave",
          optionB: "Bluetooth speaker",
          optionC: "Blender",
          correctAnswer: "Bluetooth speaker",
        },
        {
          question: "Where is face recognition technology widely used?",
          optionA: "Agriculture",
          optionB: "Criminology",
          optionC: "Education",
          correctAnswer: "Criminology",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which technology is extensively used in Google maps and online food delivery applications?",
          optionA: "Face recognition",
          optionB: "Navigation",
          optionC: "Chatbot",
          correctAnswer: "Navigation",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which Chatbot is mentioned as the most recently developed one?",
          optionA: "Siri",
          optionB: "Alexa",
          optionC: "ChatGPT",
          correctAnswer: "ChatGPT",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does voice assistance technology utilize to interact with humans?",
          optionA: "Text only",
          optionB: "Text and oral commands",
          optionC: "Oral commands only",
          correctAnswer: "Text and oral commands",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the primary function of face recognition technology in gadgets?",
          optionA: "Identifying weather patterns",
          optionB: "Recognizing faces",
          optionC: "Predicting earthquakes",
          correctAnswer: "Recognizing faces",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What role does navigation technology play in applications like Google maps?",
          optionA: "Building virtual maps",
          optionB: "Identifying changes in traffic flow",
          optionC: "Recommending better routes",
          correctAnswer: "Recommending better routes",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Initially, where was the Chatbot technology primarily used?",
          optionA: "Social media",
          optionB: "Online customer support",
          optionC: "Online shopping",
          correctAnswer: "Online customer support",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In what fields is artificial intelligence gradually making its way into?",
          optionA: "Few specific industries",
          optionB: "Every aspect of life",
          optionC: "None, it's limited to tech only",
          correctAnswer: "Every aspect of life",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Voice assistance technology interacts with humans based on __________ and __________.",
          optionA: "Audio, visuals",
          optionB: "Text, visuals",
          optionC: "Text, oral commands",
          correctAnswer: "Text, oral commands",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Face recognition technology is widely used in the field of __________.",
          optionA: "Agriculture",
          optionB: "Criminology",
          optionC: "Medicine",
          correctAnswer: "Criminology",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Navigation technology is crucial for identifying changes in __________.",
          optionA: "Weather patterns",
          optionB: "Traffic flow",
          optionC: "Social behavior",
          correctAnswer: "Traffic flow",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Chatbot technology was initially employed for online __________.",
          optionA: "Shopping",
          optionB: "Customer support",
          optionC: "Social media interaction",
          correctAnswer: "Customer support",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Artificial intelligence aims to improve efficiency and enhance human capabilities across __________ aspects of our lives.",
          optionA: "Some",
          optionB: "All",
          optionC: "Limited",
          correctAnswer: "All",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Smart gadgets based on artificial intelligence are developed to make life easier by employing various __________.",
          optionA: "Devices",
          optionB: "Technologies",
          optionC: "Functions",
          correctAnswer: "Technologies",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Face recognition technology is capable of scanning and recognizing faces from __________.",
          optionA: "Written documents",
          optionB: "Digital images or video frames",
          optionC: "Social media posts",
          correctAnswer: "Digital images or video frames",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Voice assistance technology can remember and recognize __________.",
          optionA: "Commands",
          optionB: "Voices",
          optionC: "Sounds",
          correctAnswer: "Voices",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Navigation technology is heavily utilized in applications like Google maps for recommending __________ routes.",
          optionA: "Quickest",
          optionB: "Scenic",
          optionC: "Better",
          correctAnswer: "Better",
        },
        {
          question: "ChatGPT is a recently developed __________.",
          optionA: "Navigation system",
          optionB: "Face recognition tool",
          optionC: "Chatbot",
          correctAnswer: "Chatbot",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Artificial intelligence enhances human capabilities but doesn't impact efficiency.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Voice assistance technology can only process oral commands.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Navigation technology plays a minor role in applications like Google Maps.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Face recognition technology is solely used in the field of entertainment.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "ChatGPT is an outdated technology compared to other chatbots.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Voice assistance technology cannot recognize different voices.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Navigation technology doesn't contribute to identifying traffic flow changes.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Chatbot technology was initially designed for social media interaction.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Artificial intelligence impacts only a few aspects of human life.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Face recognition technology can't scan faces from digital images.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
